<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bucharest - Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for phrases [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_Main">Main Attractions</string>
    <string name="category_Restaurants">Traditional Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_Shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="category_FreeTIme">Free Time Activities</string>

    <string name="parliament_palace">The Palace of the Parliament (Romanian: Palatul Parlamentului)
       is the seat of the Parliament of Romania. Located on Dealul Arsenalului in central Bucharest
       (Sector 5), it is the second-largest administrative building in the world,[1] after the
       Pentagon in the United States. With a height of 84 m, an area of 365,000 m2 and having a
       volume of 2,550,000 m3, it is also the fourth biggest building in the world, after the
       Vehicle Assembly Building at Kennedy Space Center in Florida, the Temple of the Feathered
       Serpent in Teotihuacan, Mexico, and the Pentagon. In terms of weight,
       the Palace of the Parliament is the heaviest building in the world, weighing in at around
       4,098,500,000 kg.</string>

    <string name="romanian_athenaeum">The Romanian Athenaeum (Romanian: Ateneul Român) is a concert
        hall in the center of Bucharest, Romania and a landmark of the Romanian capital city.
        Opened in 1888, the ornate, domed, circular building is the city main concert hall and
        home of the "George Enescu" Philharmonic and of the George Enescu annual international
        music festival.</string>

    <string name="village_museum">The Village Museum (Muzeul Satului in Romanian) is an open-air
        ethnographic museum located in the Herăstrău Park (Bucharest, Romania), showcasing
        traditional Romanian village life. The museum extends to over 100,000 m2, and contains
        272 authentic peasant farms and houses from all over Romania.</string>

    <string name="Hanul_lui_Manuc">Manuc Inn (Romanian: Hanul lui Manuc, pronounced
        [ˈ\hanu(l) luj maˈ\nuk]) was, until it was recently[when?] shut for restoration and
        refurbishment, the oldest operating hotel building in Bucharest, Romania; it also housed
        a popular restaurant, several bars, a coffee-house, and (facing the street) several stores
        and an extensive bar. Its massive, multiply balconied courtyard hosted many performances
        and fairs and was a popular place for Romanian television crews to shoot folkloric
        performances. The hotel and restaurant were closed down in 2007 for refurbishment;
        [citation needed] shops[citation needed] and a bar known both as Cafeaneaua Bucurestilor de
        Altadata ("Bucharest of Yesteryear" Cafe) and as Festival 39 remained open (though the bar
        closed in February 2010).[1] The hotel and restaurant are expected to reopen under new
        management once the restoration and refurbishment are completed.[citation needed] However,
        there appear to be disagreements between the city government and the owners about the
        legality of certain modernizations being undertaken.</string>

    <string name="Carul_cu_Bere">The Carul cu Bere (aka Carul cu Bere; "the beer wagon") is a bar
        and restaurant on Stavropoleos Street in the Lipscani district of Bucharest, Romania,
        opened in 1879[1] and moved to the current location, a gothic revival building designed
        by Austrian architect Siegfrid Kofczinsky, in 1899. It is noted for its interior decoration,
        in art nouveau style.</string>

    <string name="Restaurant_Vatra">The Vatra Restaurant opened up December 2001 and ever since it
        has been the place where the Romanian cuisine is pleasantly supplemented by the authenticity
        of the Transylvanian sets.</string>

    <string name="Baneasa_Shopping">Baneasa Shopping City is a shopping mall in Bucharest, Romania.
        Address: Șoseaua București-Ploiești 42D, București 015011</string>

    <string name="Afi_Pallace">AFI Palace Cotroceni is a shopping mall in Bucharest, Romania. It is
        located in the central-western part of the city, between the city center and two of the
        largest residential districts, Militari and Drumul Taberei.
        Address: Bulevardul Vasile Milea 4, București 061344</string>

    <string name="Promenada">Shopping mall in Bucharest, Romania
        Address: Calea Floreasca 246B, București</string>

    <string name="Herastrau">Herăstrău Park (Romanian: Parcul Herăstrău) is a large park on the
        northern side of Bucharest, Romania, around Lake Herăstrău, one of the lakes formed by the
        Colentina River. The park has an area of about 187 ha, of which 74 ha is the lake.
        Initially, the area was full of marshes, but these were drained between 1930 and 1935, and
        the park was opened in 1936. The park is divided into two zones: a rustic or natural zone
        (the Village Museum), which is left more or less undisturbed, and a public domain
        with open areas for recreation activities. Small boats are allowed on the lake.</string>

    <string name="Cismigiu">The Cișmigiu Gardens or Cișmigiu Park are a public park near the center
        of Bucharest, Romania, spanning areas on all sides of an artificial lake. The gardens
        creation was an important moment in the history of Bucharest.</string>

    <string name="Natural_History">The Grigore Antipa National Museum of Natural History is a
        Natural History museum, located in Bucharest, Romania. It was originally established as
        the National Museum of Natural History on 3 November 1834.</string>

    <string name="Palace_of_Parliament">Palace of Parliament</string>

    <string name="Romanian_Athenaeum">Romanian Athenaeum</string>

    <string name="Hanul">Hanul lui Manuc</string>

    <string name="Caru_cu_Bere">Carul cu Bere</string>

    <string name="Village_Museum">Village Museum</string>

    <string name="Rest_Vatra">Restaurant Vatra</string>

    <string name="Baneasa">Baneasa Shopping City</string>

    <string name="Afi_Pallace_Mall">Afi Palace Cotroceni</string>

    <string name="Promenada_Mall">Promenada Mall</string>

    <string name="Walk_in_Herastrau_Park">Walk in Herastrau Park</string>

    <string name="Walk_in_Cismigiu_Gardens">Walk in Cismigiu Gardens</string>

    <string name="Visit_Museum_of_Natural_History">Visit Museum of Natural History</string>


</resources>
